<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<page>
  <title>Фото</title>
  <description>Все самое новое</description>
  <content>&lt;p style="text-align: right;"&gt;&lt;img src="/image.axd?picture=/jcarousel/Основной/CrocusTL_EN-US9175103735_1920x1200.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: right;"&gt;Some of the first blooms you&amp;rsquo;ll see in spring may be crocuses. These hardy bulbs are so well known for blooming before the snow has melted, there&amp;rsquo;s even a variety called the &amp;ldquo;snow crocus.&amp;rdquo; Other varieties, including the saffron crocus (the source of the prized spice), bloom in autumn. But let&amp;rsquo;s put thoughts of fall aside today. Spring has officially arrived!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: right;"&gt;&lt;img src="/image.axd?picture=/jcarousel/Основной/FrogTadpole_EN-US10492168393_1920x1200.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: right;"&gt;Though there are some exceptions, most frogs (and toads) go through the life cycle glimpsed in progress here. When a frog&amp;rsquo;s eggs hatch, the juveniles emerge as tadpoles, looking nothing like their parents. But in time, the tadpoles will metamorphose&amp;mdash;their tails will shrink as fins become legs and they begin to take on adult frog characteristics. We&amp;rsquo;re witnessing here the braces-and-acne stage of the amphibian world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: right;"&gt;&lt;img src="/image.axd?picture=/jcarousel/Основной/CrocusTL_EN-US9175103735_1920x1200.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Limestone covers most of Gozo, one of the three populated islands in the Maltese archipelago. Mediterranean waves relentlessly pound against the shore, carving dramatic cliffs&amp;mdash;none more striking than those that form the Azure Window. The natural arch was created when two sea caves collapsed, leaving a relatively thin horizontal ledge as a bridge between the mainland and a tall stone outcropping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rock continues to fall from the underside of the arch at a rate that suggests it will collapse completely within just a few years. Given the unstable conditions, posted signs warn visitors not to walk over the top of the arch, but most any day will find thrill seekers catching the dramatic view up close&amp;mdash;while they still can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/image.axd?picture=/jcarousel/Основной/AzoresPortugal_EN-US12392527859_1920x1200.jpg" alt="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Portuguese sailors first documented Corvo Island in the mid-1300s. It&amp;rsquo;s the northernmost island in the Azores, a mid-Atlantic archipelago governed by Portugal. But the small island had likely burst up from the brine some 730,000 years ago, when the submarine volcano Monte Gorde erupted, causing the mountain&amp;rsquo;s cone to climb up above the water&amp;rsquo;s surface. Roughly 300,000 years later, another eruption created the caldera seen here. Known simply as the Caldeir&amp;atilde;o, the crater eventually developed into a peat bog with two small lakes and tiny islets. Scientists trek to Corvo Island regularly to study its unique ecology and volcanic structure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[CAROUSEL:Album1]&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <keywords>Новое Фото</keywords>
  <slug>Новое</slug>
  <parent>00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000</parent>
  <isfrontpage>False</isfrontpage>
  <showinlist>False</showinlist>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>True</isdeleted>
  <sortorder>0</sortorder>
  <datecreated>2016-04-06 15:14:00</datecreated>
  <datemodified>2016-04-08 19:07:35</datemodified>
</page>